mindtree.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy | Mindtree

**The effective date of this Policy is May 17, 2018**

Your privacy is important to us. Mindtree Limited and its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (consisting of Bluefin Solutions limited and/or Magnet 360 LLC) hereinafter referred as ‘Mindtree,’ is committed to respect your privacy while using our website. This policy applies to information collected by us on our website.

**Definitions**

"Personally Identifiable Information"(or ‘PII”) means any information that relates to a natural person, which, either directly or indirectly, in combination with other information available or likely to be available with a corporate body, is capable of identifying such person.

**The information we collect:**

We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information about you, unless you choose to fill out your information on this website through specific provided forms. In general, you may browse our website without providing any Personal Identifiable Information about yourself. We do automatically collect certain information when you visit our website such as the type of operating system, the type of browser you are using, your IP address in order to provide better usability and personalized experience.

Mindtree shall only process the received information pursuant to pursue our legitimate business interests for establishing communication with prospective customers and personnel with general/ business inquiries.

**How we normally use information about you**

We use certain information to analyze site usage for us to improve our website.

We use Personally Identifiable Information you provide solely to respond to your inquiry or to process an application form you have completed on our website or to respond to any legal process or as required by law in response to any court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency or to take action against any illegal activity and to address any potential threat to the physical safety of a person.

**Information sharing**

We may share your Personal Identifiable Information within Mindtree, Mindtree group or with any of our subsidiaries and very occasionally our business partners, service vendors or authorized third-party agents located in any part of the world for the purposes of data processing, enrichment, storage, or to provide a requested service or transaction, after ensuring that such entities are contractually bound by data privacy obligations.

Where we transfer Personally Identifiable Information outside of EU, we either transfer these Information to countries that provide an adequate level of protection (as determined by the European Commission) or have appropriate safeguards in place.

**Your rights**

You may have certain rights relating to your Personally Identifiable Information provided for under applicable law. These are the right to:

• Request access to your Personally Identifiable Information and the processing activities on the same.

• Request that your Personally Identifiable Information is rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete

• Request erasure of your Personally Identifiable Information in certain circumstances.

• Request restriction of the processing of your Personally Identifiable Information in certain circumstances.

• Object to the processing of your Personally Identifiable Information in certain circumstances.

• Receive your Personally Identifiable Information provided to us as a controller in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format in certain circumstances.

• Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

• Withdraw your consent provided at any time by contacting us.

To exercise the rights outlined above in respect of your Personally Identifiable Information please contact the details available in the contact section below. We will endeavor to respond to you within appropriate as required by the law.

**Right to opt out and withdrawal**

Mindtree respects your privacy considerations and hence provides you an option to refuse to provide your Personally Identifiable Information or information sought to be collected.

You also have the option to subscribe/opt-in to receive newsletters, new alerts and marketing content. You can always opt-out of such options by writing to Dataprotection.Office@mindtree.com or click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of an email newsletter received by you from us. Mindtree shall adhere to your preferences.

**Authenticity**

Mindtree shall not be responsible for the authenticity of the information and it is your duty to ensure that the information provided is authentic.

**Cookies and other technologies**

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that website can remember who you are. Please read our Cookie Policy carefully for more details about the information we collect when you use this site.

**Data storage and retention**

Your PII is stored in databases located at India and on the servers of the cloud-based database management services that Mindtree engages.

Mindtree shall retain your PII Personal Information pursuant to the business purposes and in line with our retention policies.

PII received from prospective customers shall be retained for the duration of the prospective customer’s business relationship with the Mindtree.

**Protection of minor’s information**

The website is not directed to children under the age of sixteen (16). Mindtree does not knowingly solicit PII from or market to anyone under sixteen (16) years of age. If you believe that we have received information from a minor, please notify us immediately and we will ensure that reasonable efforts will be made by us to delete such information from our database.

**Links to third party websites**

Our website may contain links to other sites including social media sites, whose information practices may be different from ours. You should read such third party’s websites privacy notices and Mindtree does not control those sites or their privacy practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites.

**Our commitment to security**

Mindtree utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect. Mindtree takes reasonable steps to ensure that all dealings in personally identifiable information is processed fairly & lawfully after receiving consent of the information provider. Mindtree may retain your personally identifiable information as long as there is a business requirement, or if otherwise required under applicable laws.

**Grievance Redressal**

Any grievance or complaint, in relation to processing of information, should be sent to Mindtree in writing to following contact email ID. Grievance shall be redressed as expeditiously as possible.

The details of the Grievance Officer are as follows:

**Srinivasa Rao Kottamasu**

Email: Dataprotection.Office@mindtree.com

Secondary email: Srinivasa.Kottamasu@mindtree.com

Address - Global Village, RVCE Post Mysore Road

Bangalore 560059, INDIA

**Changes to this Policy**

Please note that this policy may change from time to time. Please review the policy periodically for changes.
